payza.eu 2016-04-10

# Payza | Send Money, Receive Payment, Money Transfer, Shop & Sell Online

This privacy policy applies to [www.Payza.com](https://www.payza.com/) , owned and operated by MH Pillars Ltd. Henceforward “Payza” ,“we”, “us” or “our” refers collectively to Payza.com, MH Pillars Ltd., its officers, directors, agents, subsidiaries, joint ventures, employees and suppliers. This policy describes how Payza collects and uses the personal information you (the person or entity using this service) provide on our web site, www.payza.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

**We collect the following personal information from you:**

  * Contact Information, such as name, email address, mailing address and phone number
  * Billing Information, such as credit card number and billing address
  * Financial Information, such as bank or brokerage account numbers, and types of investments
  * Driver's License Number
  * Unique Identifiers, such as user name, account number and password
  * Preferences Information, such as product wish lists, order history and marketing preferences.
  * Business Information, such as company name, company size and business type

Additionally, as is true of most websites, we gather anonymous, aggregate information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit page, operating system, date/time stamp and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to any personal information.

**We use the information we collect to:**

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our website and marketing efforts
  * Send you corporate information or updates, such as a newsletter
  * Conduct research and analysis
  * Display content based upon your interests

### Information Obtained from Third Parties

We obtain credit information about you from an outside credit reporting agency to help us with customer authentication and credit-related decisions.

### Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities, such as ID verification and job applicant tracking. Our shopping cart is hosted by our e-commerce solutions provider. They host our ordering system, and collect your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order. These third party verification and identity authentication services companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us

**We may also disclose your personal information:**

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or a similar legal process;
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;
  * If Payza is involved in a merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of its assets. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as the choices you may have regarding the sharing of your personal information;
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

### Communications

We may send you email messages about our company, our platform and our Services, as well as email messages about products and services of selected third parties. By accepting the User Agreement, you consent to receive these messages. As a member, you can opt out of receiving commercial messages by following the ‘unsubscribe’ link found in each communication. Please note that we reserve the right to send you service-related communications, including service announcements and administrative messages, relating either to your account or to your transactions, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them unless you close your account.

### User Access and Choice

If your personal information changes, or if you wish to discontinue the use of our service, you may correct, delete, update, amend or request to deactivate your account by effectuating changes in your account settings page, by emailing our Customer Support at [info@payza.com](mailto:info@payza.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with service. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. 

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Respecting your right to privacy, we will remove you from our mailing lists should you wish to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or by contacting us at

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Mhpillars, our affiliates, analytics. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. We use cookies for saving authentication values and saving referral information . Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

### Behavioral Advertising

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Local Shared Objects - Flash Cookies

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 or Flash to store some of your preferences and to display content based upon personalized to your preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 or Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.

To manage Flash LSOs please click here: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html 

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number or other financial information) on our forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, however, is 100% secure. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at <https://www.payza.com/support>

In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy policy and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy policy before providing your information.

### Additional Policy Information

**Links to Third Party Sites**

Our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Payza. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of every website you visit.

**Testimonials**

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at info@payza.com.

### Blog / Forum

Our website offers publicly accessible blog and forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. _To request the removal of your personal information from our blog, contact us at[info@payza.com](mailto:info@payza.com) _ In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will notify you as to the reason. 

### Social Media Widgets

Our website includes widgets, interactive mini-programs that run on our website that provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through these widgets. Cookies may also be set by a widget to optimize its functionality. Information collected by a widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

### Notification of Privacy Policy Changes

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to any changes being effectuated. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information regarding our privacy practices.

### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

**Payza**  
Secure Mail Box #620 - 2348 Chemin Lucerne  
Montreal, QC, Canada H3R-2J8  
Email: [info@payza.com](mailto:info@payza.com)
